A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Hospital, Collected Reprints, Series 4 FA909
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Hospital, Collected Reprints, Series 4
1909-1940
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Cole, Rufus
Rockefeller University
FA909
2.4 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage cartons
2 standard record storage cartons.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 430-4
Arrangement
Series 4 is arranged in chronological order by subject.
Scope and Contents
Reprints of published works from the Hospital of The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research collected and bound and indexed by subject. Indexing also by author.
All volumes have a dedication in honor of Rufus Cole.
Conditions Governing Access note
This material is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
The Rockefeller University records, Hospital is arranged in four series:
Series 1: General Files. Series 2: Administrative Correspondence. Series 3: Subject Files. Series 4: Collected Reprints.
Series 3 is closed to scholarly research pending further processing.
Other Finding Aids
FA228 Rockefeller University records, Hospital, General Files, Series 1.
FA837 Rockefeller University records, Hospital, Administrative Correspondence, Series 2.
FA838 Rockefeller University records, Hospital, Subject Files, Series 3.
Medical research; Medical technology; Medical education; Operations management; Hospitals; Medical care; Medicine, Preventive; Medical sciences
- Collected reprints, 1909-1940; 4; 11 volumes
  - Indexes, 3 volumes
    Scope and Contents
    As of March 1975 no clue found as to volumes which these three indexes refer to however they serve as good listings to scientific work done in the Hospital.
    Included are biographical sketches of hospital staff.
    Arrangement
    Arrangements are by author and also by subject.
    - 1910-1920 (Box 1)
    - 1920-1930 (Box 1)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 1)
  - Studies on respiratory disease, 6 volumes
    - 1920 January-1930 January, 3 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1930 January-1934 January (Box 1)
    - 1934 January-1936 December (Box 2)
    - 1936 December-1940 January (Box 2)
  - Papers on pneumonia, 2 volumes
    - 1909-1916 (Box 2)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 2)